https://www.abbeyroad.com/terms

General
This website is owned and operated by Virgin Records Limited t/a Abbey Road Studios, a Universal Music Group company (“Universal”).
The information, artwork, text, video, audio, pictures, software and other intellectual property (collectively, "Materials") contained on the Website are protected by copyright and international laws. You may only access and use the Materials for personal use. You may not otherwise reproduce, distribute, publicly perform, publicly display, modify or create derivative works of the Materials (or authorise others to) for commercial gain, unless authorised by the appropriate copyright owner(s).
Framing of the Website is permitted only with Universal's express agreement, and any stipulation on how the framing will be displayed or made available on any third party site shall be at Universal's sole discretion. Universal reserves the right to withhold consent for any reason and any failure to monitor or control each instance of framing shall not be considered a waiver of any of Universal's rights. Any framing by a third party shall not imply the endorsement or sponsorship of Universal.
You expressly agree that use of the Website and related services is at your sole risk. The Website, Materials and related services are provided on an "as is" and "as available" basis. Universal makes no representations or warranties with regard to the Website or any Materials therein, whether express or implied, arising by law or otherwise, including, without limitation, any implied warranty of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or non-infringement or any implied warranty arising out of course of performance, course of dealing or usage of trade.
By using the Website, Materials or related services, you agree that Universal will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature whatsoever and howsoever arising out of or in connection with the viewing, use or performance of the Website, Materials or related services whether due to inaccuracy, error, omission or any other cause.
Universal reserves the right to change any content on this Website, including but limited to revising and/or deleting or adding features or information without prior notice to users, if, however, you have any queries or comments about this Website and/or its content please let us know by sending us an email on info@umusic.com. By using this Website you agree to the Terms of Use. Universal reserves the right to prevent access to any user who is found to be in breach of these Terms of Use.
If any provision of these Terms of Use is held to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be struck out and the remaining provisions shall be enforced.
Universal's failure to act with respect to a breach by you or others does not waive its right to act with respect to subsequent or similar breaches. Changes may be made to these Terms of Use from time to time. These terms of use are governed in all aspects by the Laws of England and Wales. Legal proceedings related to the matters set out in the terms of use shall be brought and adjudicated solely in the courts of England and Wales
Links
This Website may contain links to other Websites. Universal is not responsible for or liable for the content or Terms of Use and practises of other Websites. All external Websites are accessed at the users own risk.
Cookies
Universal sometimes use cookies. A cookie is a small text file that can be stored on your computer's hard drive. It may be stored and updated at various times as you access the website. Each time you visit the website, the server may deliver certain customised information to your computer based on the data stored in your cookie. This allows Universal to tailor the service to your preferences. You are not obliged to accept a cookie and you may modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. If you wish to purchase any items on the Website you need to ensure that cookies are enabled. If, however, you do not want to accept cookies please use the help tools provided with your internet browser to find out how to achieve this. We never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer which was not originally contained in the cookie. We use cookies and IP addresses for system administration and to monitor aggregate non-personalised information (such as anonymous statistics related to the take up or use of services, or to patterns of browsing). Certain non-personal information about users is recorded by the standard operation of Universal's internet servers. Examples of this type of information include the type of browsers being used, its operating system and the domain names (not e-mail addresses, where possible) of users. Universal is part of a worldwide group of companies, it may be necessary from time to time for information to be transferred from the point of collection to a server located in another jurisdiction. Information will only be so transferred in circumstances where it is necessary to achieve the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or the purposes made known to users at the time information is collected.
Purchaching content, products or sercives on the website
If you wish to purchase any content, products or services offered on this Website you will be asked to supply certain information. You will be asked to provide your name and email address and depending on the method of payment you will be asked to provide details of either your credit card or your mobile phone. Access to certain content or products may be age restricted. Where any such restriction applies you will be asked to confirm that you are old enough to purchase the items or purchase and view the content as appropriate.
Message boards/webchat
We may monitor any message board and/or webchat area which exists on this Website though we are not under any obligation to do so. We advise you to use care and discretion when disclosing personal information on any message board or on any chat area on this Website as other users may collect and use this information and this may result in users receiving unsolicited messages from other people. Please refer to the Safe Surfing Guide on this Website for some guidance.
Users must not upload, post, publish or transmit any unlawful, fraudulent, libellous, defamatory, obscene, threatening abuse or otherwise objectionable information of any kind, in any area of the Website including on message boards and in webchat areas. Universal considers as constituting objectionable information any information which constitutes or encourages the breach of any intellectual property right including copyright whether such right is owned by Universal or any third party.
Universal reserves the right to remove or edit (without notice) any item of information which it considers to be in breach of these Terms of Use and to disclose any information as necessary or appropriate to satisfy any law, regulation or other governmental request. Universal also reserves the right to bar any user from the message board and webchat areas of the Website if he or she uploads, posts, publishes or transmits objectionable information in these areas.
Any user of this Website should contact us immediately by email if he or she feels that any message posted on any message board or the content of any webchat is objectionable in any way. We will then endeavour to remove the objectionable messages if we consider it to be necessary.
Use by children
If you are under the age of 16 you should obtain the consent of your parents or legal guardians for submitting any personal information to this Website.
Children under the age of 13 should not submit any personal information without the written consent of their parents or legal guardian. If you are a child under 13 and want to submit personal information to us please ask your parent or legal guardian to send us an email at info@umusic.com specifying that they consent to us collecting your personal information through this Website. You and your parents or legal guardians should also read the Safe Surfing Guide on the Website. Parents or legal guardians may review or change the personal information of their children or refuse further collection of any such information by sending an email to us at info@umusic.com.
Research
We are always looking to improve our user experience on the website and to find out more about our users' tastes in music. We conduct research with Universal Music by sending out questionnaires from time to time by email. If you receive one you do not need to complete it if you do not want to. If at any time you wish to stop receiving research questionnaires you can reply to the email address at the bottom of the email you receive. Alternatively email us at info@umusic.com and tell us you do not want to receive any more questionnaires.
Forewarding web pages
If we provide you with the opportunity to email a web page to another person, we will need to collect your email address and the email address of those to whom you send the page. We will use the email addresses collected this way for no other purpose expect to send the web page, and the addresses will be deleted once the page has been sent unless you have opted in to receive information and promotions from us as set out above using the same email address, in which case we will retain your email address for this purpose unless and until you notify us that you wish to stop receiving information.
Financial
If we make a sale to you on this site we may use your financial information (including credit card transactions) to check your qualifications and Bill you for and otherwise facilitate your purchase of products and services. When you make a purchase on the Site, we will provide your financial information (including credit card transactions) to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine is necessary to process your transactions. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process the transaction. Also, depending on the circumstances of our arrangements, we may share your financial information (including credit card transactions) with applicable Event Partners, primarily but not exclusively for facilitating "will call" ticket pick up and dispute resolution and customer service at the event venue on the date of the event. When you purchase products or services of third parties (such as magazine subscriptions) offered on eh Site, we will provide your financial information (including credit card transactions) to those third parties. Any of these various third parties are authorised to use your financial information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control.
How we use and when we share broad demographic information
We may use, and may transfer to others to use, broad demographic information that may include data from your activity at the Site, but not personal information. For example, we use broad demographic information to tailor the site to the interests of our visitors, and we may share it with advertisers and other third parties so that they can tailor their advertisements and communications to the appropriate audience. We reserve the right to use such broad demographic information, and to allow others to make use of it, without limitation or restriction, and without further notice to you, in our sole and absolute discretion and is the sole and absolute discretion of those with whom we share such information.
Third parties
When we include links to other internet sites, on this site and in our newsletters and other communications, we do so solely as a convenience to our visitors. Operators of such linked sites may acquire personal information about you through registration procedures or other means and may use that information in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control. Your access and use of linked sites is solely at your own risk.
Security
Whenever we obtain your personal information we take reasonable precautions to protect it from unauthorised access or disclosure, but we cannot act as insurers of the security of your personal information transmitted over the internet. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorised third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or missions beyond our reasonable control.
Disclosure
If you are a member of the artist community you should note that when you complete your member profile this information may be viewed by other members. Accordingly you should not provide any information in your member profile that you do not wish to share with third parties and you should have no privacy expectations with respect to the information contained within it. You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information online in a public accessible area, such as in your member profile, a message board or chat room, that information may be collected an used by others. We do not control the actions of our visitors. If you disclose personal information in your member profile message board or any other public accessible place on the internet you do so at your own risk and should understand that your submitted information may be collected and used by others to send you unsolicited messages, advertisements, or for other purposes. Please remember the protection of your privacy begins with you. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any password you use to register, and you should always be careful and responsible whenever disclosing information online.
Finally
Universal may make changes to this terms and conditions and privacy policy from time to time but will not change the way we use your information provided previously without your express consent. If any provision of this privacy policy is held to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be struck out and the remaining provisions shall be enforced. Universal's failure to act with respect to a breach by you or others does not waive its right to act with respect to subsequent or similar breaches. The privacy policy is governed in all respects by the laws of England and Wales. Legal proceedings related to the matters set out in the Privacy Policy shall be brought in and adjudicated solely in the courts of England and Wales.
Download T&Cs
Online Mastering, Online Mixing , Studio & Topline
×
Ok
Yes
No
Cancel
×
